window.QUIZ_NUMERAL2 = {
    "title": "Arabic Numerals",
    "version": 1,
    "count": 34,
    "questions": [
      {"id":1,"question":"١١","options":["أحَدَ عَشَرَ","اِثنا عَشَرَ","عَشَرَةٌ","ثَلاثَةَ عَشَرَ"],"answer":"أحَدَ عَشَرَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":2,"question":"١٢","options":["أحَدَ عَشَرَ","ثَلاثَةَ عَشَرَ","اِثنا عَشَرَ","أربَعَةَ عَشَرَ"],"answer":"اِثنا عَشَرَ","answer_index":2},
      {"id":3,"question":"١٣","options":["ثَلاثَةَ عَشَرَ","خَمسَةَ عَشَرَ","اِثنا عَشَرَ","أربَعَةَ عَشَرَ"],"answer":"ثَلاثَةَ عَشَرَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":4,"question":"١٤","options":["ثَلاثَةَ عَشَرَ","أربَعَةَ عَشَرَ","خَمسَةَ عَشَرَ","سِتَّةَ عَشَرَ"],"answer":"أربَعَةَ عَشَرَ","answer_index":1},
      {"id":5,"question":"١٥","options":["سِتَّةَ عَشَرَ","خَمسَةَ عَشَرَ","أربَعَةَ عَشَرَ","سَبعَةَ عَشَرَ"],"answer":"خَمسَةَ عَشَرَ","answer_index":1},
      {"id":6,"question":"١٦","options":["سِتَّةَ عَشَرَ","ثَمانِيَةَ عَشَرَ","خَمسَةَ عَشَرَ","سَبعَةَ عَشَرَ"],"answer":"سِتَّةَ عَشَرَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":7,"question":"١٧","options":["سَبعَةَ عَشَرَ","سِتَّةَ عَشَرَ","ثَمانِيَةَ عَشَرَ","تِسعَةَ عَشَرَ"],"answer":"سَبعَةَ عَشَرَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":8,"question":"١٨","options":["تِسعَةَ عَشَرَ","سَبعَةَ عَشَرَ","ثَمانِيَةَ عَشَرَ","سِتَّةَ عَشَرَ"],"answer":"ثَمانِيَةَ عَشَرَ","answer_index":2},
      {"id":9,"question":"١٩","options":["ثَمانِيَةَ عَشَرَ","تِسعَةَ عَشَرَ","سَبعَةَ عَشَرَ","عِشرونَ"],"answer":"تِسعَةَ عَشَرَ","answer_index":1},
      {"id":10,"question":"٢٠","options":["عِشرونَ","ثَلاثونَ","أربَعونَ","عَشَرَةٌ"],"answer":"عِشرونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":11,"question":"٣٠","options":["ثَلاثونَ","عِشرونَ","أربَعونَ","خَمسونَ"],"answer":"ثَلاثونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":12,"question":"٤٠","options":["خَمسونَ","أربَعونَ","ثَلاثونَ","سِتّونَ"],"answer":"أربَعونَ","answer_index":1},
      {"id":13,"question":"٥٠","options":["خَمسونَ","سِتّونَ","أربَعونَ","سَبعونَ"],"answer":"خَمسونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":14,"question":"٦٠","options":["سَبعونَ","سِتّونَ","خَمسونَ","ثَمانونَ"],"answer":"سِتّونَ","answer_index":1},
      {"id":15,"question":"٧٠","options":["سَبعونَ","سِتّونَ","ثَمانونَ","تِسعونَ"],"answer":"سَبعونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":15,"question":"٨٠","options":["تِسعونَ","ثَمانونَ","سَبعونَ","سِتّونَ"],"answer":"ثَمانونَ","answer_index":1},
      {"id":16,"question":"٩٠","options":["ثَمانونَ","سَبعونَ","تِسعونَ","مِائَةٌ"],"answer":"تِسعونَ","answer_index":2},
      {"id":17,"question":"١٠٠","options":["تِسعونَ","مِائَةٌ","عَشَرَةٌ","خَمسونَ"],"answer":"مِائَةٌ","answer_index":1},
      {"id":18,"question":"٣٧","options":["سَبعَةٌ وَثَلاثونَ","ثَلاثَةٌ وَسَبعونَ","خَمسَةٌ وَثَلاثونَ","تِسعَةٌ وَثَلاثونَ"],"answer":"سَبعَةٌ وَثَلاثونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":19,"question":"٥٢","options":["اِثنانِ وَخَمسونَ","خَمسَةٌ وَعِشرونَ","خَمسَةٌ وَخَمسونَ","اِثنانِ وَأربَعونَ"],"answer":"اِثنانِ وَخَمسونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":20,"question":"٦٨","options":["ثَمانِيَةٌ وَسِتّونَ","سِتَّةٌ وَثَمانونَ","سِتَّةٌ وَسِتّونَ","ثَمانِيَةٌ وَسَبعونَ"],"answer":"ثَمانِيَةٌ وَسِتّونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":21,"question":"٩١","options":["واحِدٌ وَتِسعونَ","تِسعَةَ عَشَرَ","تِسعونَ","مِائَةٌ"],"answer":"واحِدٌ وَتِسعونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":22,"question":"٤٤","options":["أربَعَةٌ وَأربَعونَ","أربَعَةَ عَشَرَ","أربَعونَ","أربَعَةٌ وَخَمسونَ"],"answer":"أربَعَةٌ وَأربَعونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":23,"question":"٧٩","options":["تِسعَةٌ وَسَبعونَ","سَبعَةٌ وَتِسعونَ","سَبعَةٌ وَسَبعونَ","تِسعَةٌ وَسِتّونَ"],"answer":"تِسعَةٌ وَسَبعونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":24,"question":"٢١","options":["واحِدٌ وَعِشرونَ","عِشرونَ وَواحِدٌ","اِثنانِ وَعِشرونَ","واحِدٌ وَثَلاثونَ"],"answer":"واحِدٌ وَعِشرونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":25,"question":"٢٨","options":["ثَمانِيَةٌ وَعِشرونَ","ثَمانونَ وَاِثنانِ","سِتَّةٌ وَعِشرونَ","ثَمانِيَةٌ وَثَلاثونَ"],"answer":"ثَمانِيَةٌ وَعِشرونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":26,"question":"٣٣","options":["ثَلاثَةٌ وَثَلاثونَ","ثَلاثونَ وَثَلاثَةٌ","أربَعَةٌ وَثَلاثونَ","ثَلاثَةٌ وَأربَعونَ"],"answer":"ثَلاثَةٌ وَثَلاثونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":27,"question":"٤٥","options":["خَمسَةٌ وَأربَعونَ","أربَعَةٌ وَخَمسونَ","خَمسونَ وَخَمسَةٌ","خَمسَةَ عَشَرَ"],"answer":"خَمسَةٌ وَأربَعونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":28,"question":"٥٧","options":["سَبعَةٌ وَخَمسونَ","خَمسَةٌ وَسَبعونَ","سَبعونَ وَسَبعَةٌ","سَبعَةَ عَشَرَ"],"answer":"سَبعَةٌ وَخَمسونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":29,"question":"٦٣","options":["ثَلاثَةٌ وَسِتّونَ","سِتَّةٌ وَثَلاثونَ","ثَلاثونَ وَثَلاثَةٌ","ثَلاثَةَ عَشَرَ"],"answer":"ثَلاثَةٌ وَسِتّونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":30,"question":"٧٤","options":["أربَعَةٌ وَسَبعونَ","سَبعَةٌ وَأربَعونَ","سَبعونَ وَأربَعَةٌ","أربَعَةَ عَشَرَ"],"answer":"أربَعَةٌ وَسَبعونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":31,"question":"٨٦","options":["سِتَّةٌ وَثَمانونَ","ثَمانِيَةٌ وَسِتّونَ","سِتّونَ وَسِتَّةٌ","سِتَّةَ عَشَرَ"],"answer":"سِتَّةٌ وَثَمانونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":32,"question":"٩٥","options":["خَمسَةٌ وَتِسعونَ","تِسعَةٌ وَخَمسونَ","تِسعونَ وَخَمسَةٌ","خَمسَةَ عَشَرَ"],"answer":"خَمسَةٌ وَتِسعونَ","answer_index":0},
      {"id":33,"question":"٤٨","options":["ثَمانِيَةٌ وَأربَعونَ","أربَعَةٌ وَثَمانونَ","أربَعونَ وَثَمانِيَةٌ","ثَمانِيَةَ عَشَرَ"],"answer":"ثَمانِيَةٌ وَأربَعونَ","answer_index":0}
    ]
  };
